Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
- Switchmen's Union of North America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 4)
- Switchmen's Union of North America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 5)
- Switchmen's Union of North America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 6)
- ACWA, Publication (Box 662, Folder 7)
- Order of Railway Conductores, Publication (Box 662, Folder 8)
- Hotel Association of New York, Publication (Box 662, Folder 9)
- Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 662, Folder 10)
- Newspaper Guild, Publication (Box 662, Folder 11)
- Amalgamated Transit Union, Publication (Box 662, Folder 12)
- Professional and Technical Engineers, Publication (Box 662, Folder 13)
- American Postal Workers Union, Publication (Box 662, Folder 14)
- Utility Workers Union of America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 15)
- California AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 662, Folder 16)
- United Steelworkers of America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 17)
- Eastern Millwrights Regional Conference, Publication (Box 662, Folder 18)
- Laborers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 662, Folder 19)
- UE (Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 662, Folder 20)
- CSEA, Publication (Box 662, Folder 21)
- International Labor Communications Association, Publication (Box 662, Folder 22)
- King County Labor Council, Publication (Box 662, Folder 23)
- UAW, Publication (Box 662, Folder 24)
- International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Shipbuilders, Blacksmiths, Forgers, and Helpers, Publication (Box 662, Folder 25)
- Ontario Secondary School Teachers Federation, Publication (Box 662, Folder 26)
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 662, Folder 27)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 662, Folder 28)
- National Maritime Union, Publication (Box 662, Folder 29)
- American Federation of Grain Millers, Publication (Box 662, Folder 30)
- Building Service Employees, Publication (Box 662, Folder 31)
- ACWA, Publication (Box 662, Folder 32)
- International Association of Machinists, Publication (Box 662, Folder 33)
- IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers), Publication (Box 662, Folder 34)
- Factory Bakers' Union, Publication (Box 662, Folder 35)
- BLE (Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers), Publication (Box 662, Folder 36)
- International Printing Pressmen and Assistants' Union, Publication (Box 662, Folder 37)
- Airline Pilots Association (APA), Publication (Box 662, Folder 38)
- ACWA, Publication (Box 662, Folder 39)
- 1199, New York's Health & Human Service Union, Publication (Box 663, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Our Life and Times, 2006; Publication (Box 663, Folder 1)
    Author: 1199, New York's Health & Human Service Union
- United Federation of Teachers, Publication (Box 663, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Organized Labor, 1980; Publication (Box 663, Folder 2)
    Author: United Federation of Teachers
- United Transportation Union, Publication (Box 663, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report on the Proposed Collective Bargaining Agreements between the Manhattan and Bronx Surface Transit Operating Authority and Supervisors Organization, 1981; Publication (Box 663, Folder 3)
    Author: United Transportation Union
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 663, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Award between the Western Railroads and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1915; Publication (Box 663, Folder 4)
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 663, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Brief in the Matter of the Arbitration between Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and The Railroad Officials, 1912; Publication (Box 663, Folder 5)
    Author: Warren S. Stone
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 663, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Directory, 1989-1994 (Box 663, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 663, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers vs. Chicago and North Western Railway Co., 1914-1921 (Box 663, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 663, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1987-1996 (Box 663, Folder 8)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 664, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineers Journal, 1997-2005 (Box 664, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 664, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Arbitration Western Railroads Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers with Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1913- 1914 (Box 664, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 664, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Arbitration between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen and ther Eastern Railroad, 1913; Publication (Box 664, Folder 3)
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 665, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Arbitration between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Eastern Railroads, 1912; Publication (Box 665, Folder 1)
    Language: Spanish:English.
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 665, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings between the Eastern Railroads, 1913; Publication (Box 665, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 665, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Arbitration between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the western Railroads, 1914-1915 (Box 665, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 666, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Arbitration between the Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers and the Western Railroads, 1914-1915 (Box 666, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 667, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Proceedings Fourth Quinquennial Convention, 1986-1996 (Box 667, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.), Publication (Box 667, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Secretary-Treasurer, 1981-1991 (Box 667, Folder 3)
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.): Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 667, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Rulings as to the Maning or Application of the Award, 1915; Publication (Box 667, Folder 4)
    Author: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.): Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers (U.S.): Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 667, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Selected Awards of the first Division National Railroad Adjustment Board on Investigation and Discipline Procedures, 1974; Publication (Box 667, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 667, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Argument and Brief, 1918; Publication (Box 667, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 667, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Education Program 38th BLF&E Convention, Publication (Box 667, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 667, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Federal Legislation, ETC., 1940; Publication (Box 667, Folder 8)
    Notes: Jan.
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 667, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Thirty-Third Convention, 1937; Publication (Box 667, Folder 9)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 668, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Schedules of Rules, Rates, and Regulations for the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, 1891; Publication (Box 668, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 668, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report to the Convention, 1937-1968 (Box 668, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 668, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Along the Way, 1981-1986 (Box 668, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 668, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: BMWE Journal, 2001-2011 (Box 668, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 669, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1938-1944 (Box 669, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 670, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1945-1958 (Box 670, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 671, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1959-1972 (Box 671, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 672, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Railway Journal, 1924-1987 (Box 672, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 673, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railway Maintenance of Way Employes Journal, 1926-1933 (Box 673, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 673, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Rates of Pay of Railroad Maintenance of Way Employes, 1925; Publication (Box 673, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 674, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Rates of Pay of Railroad Maintenance of Way Employes, 1925; Publication (Box 674, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, Publication (Box 674, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Scoreboard, 1960-1980 (Box 674, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen, Publication (Box 674, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Signalman's Journal, 1980-1983 (Box 674, Folder 3)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, Publication (Box 675, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Signalman's Journal, 1984-1997 (Box 675, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 676, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Railroad Wage Movement, 1941-1951 (Box 676, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 676, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Secretary and Treasurer, 1946-1959 (Box 676, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America, Publication (Box 676, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Signalman's Journal, 1979-1987 (Box 676, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 677, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Secretary and Treasurer, 1960-1963 (Box 677, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 677, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Secretary and Treasurer, 1964-1969 (Box 677, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 677, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the General Secretary and Treasurer, 1964; Publication (Box 677, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 677, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Report of the President, 1946-1948 (Box 677, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 677, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report of the President, 1950-1952 (Box 677, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 677, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of the President, 1953-1955 (Box 677, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 677, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Report of the President, 1956-1958 (Box 677, Folder 7)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Transcript of Proceedings, Official Papers, and Award of the Board of Arbitration, 1926; Publication (Box 678, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: U.S. Wage-1960-Rules Movement-Establishment of Commission to Review Rules, 1959-1961 (Box 678, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the Committee on th Regulation of Wages and Conditions of Service in the Road Motor Transport Industry (Goods), 1937; Publication (Box 678, Folder 3)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, Publication (Box 678, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, appellants, v. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Company [et al] appellees, 1965; Publication (Box 678, Folder 4)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Utah Copper Company v. Railroad Retirement Board, Publication (Box 678, Folder 5)
- Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen [et al] appellants, v. Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad Companies, 1967; Publication (Box 678, Folder 6)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Wartime Wages and Railroad Labor, 1944; Publication (Box 678, Folder 7)
    Author: A.F. Whitney
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Report of the Legislative Board, 1954-1959 (Box 678, Folder 8)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Publication (Box 678, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Report of the Legislative Board, 1961-1965 (Box 678, Folder 9)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, Publication (Box 678, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Grand President's Monthly Bulletin, 1937-1940 (Box 678, Folder 10)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, Publication (Box 679, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Grand President's Monthly Bulletin, 1941-1950 (Box 679, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, Publication (Box 680, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1962-1975 (Box 680, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railway and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station EmployeeBrotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 681, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1951-1961 (Box 681, Folder 1)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, Publication (Box 682, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Bulletin, 1976-1986 (Box 682, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, Publication (Box 682, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Interchange, 1985-2001 (Box 682, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 683, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Interchange, 2001-2005 (Box 683, Folder 1)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 683, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: International President's Bulletin, 1987-1991 (Box 683, Folder 2)
- Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employes, Publication (Box 683, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Patrolmen's Newsbeat, 1987; Publication (Box 683, Folder 3)
    Notes: Spring
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 683, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Bottle Maker, 1921-1924 (Box 683, Folder 4)
    Author: Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 683, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: GBBA Horizons, 1963-1973 (Box 683, Folder 5)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 684, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: GBBA Horizons, 1974-1982 (Box 684, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 684, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers Journal, 1917-1943 (Box 684, Folder 2)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 685, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers Journal, 1944-1965 (Box 685, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 685, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Record of Pre-Conference of the Pacific Coast Local Unions, 1942-1946 (Box 685, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 685, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of the Auditor, 1946; Publication (Box 685, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 685, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Executive Board Report, 1971; Publication (Box 685, Folder 4)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 685, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Worker's Report of the Sessions of the Final Wage Conference, 1920; Publication (Box 685, Folder 5)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 685, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report of the Sessions of the Conference Held Between Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada and American Flint Glass Worker's Union of North America, 1911; Publication (Box 685, Folder 6)
    Notes: Atlantic City, NJ Sept 11-13
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 685, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Proceedings of the Special Convention, 1971; Publication (Box 685, Folder 7)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 685, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: To the Delegates of the Twentieth Convention, 1941-1953 (Box 685, Folder 8)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 686, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Workers Report of Wage Conference, 1923-1926 (Box 686, Folder 1)
- Industrial Workers of the World, Publication (Box 686, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: One Big Union Monthly, 1919-1938 (Box 686, Folder 2)
    Author: Industrial Workers of the World
    Notes: 1919, 1920, 1937-1938
- Industrial Workers of the World, Publication (Box 686, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Starving Amidst Too Much & Other IWW Writings on the Food Industry, 2005; Publication (Box 686, Folder 3)
    Author: T-Bone Slin, L.S. Chumley, Jim Seymour, Jack Sheridan
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 686, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Joint Meeting of the International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers and the Pacific Coast Association of Pulp and Paper Manufacturers, 1943; Publication (Box 686, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 686, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Pre-Wage Conference, 1962; Publication (Box 686, Folder 5)
    Author: ]International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers
- International Brotherhood of Pulp, Sulphite, and Paper Mill Workers, Publication (Box 686, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Minutes of the Pre-Wage Conference, 1944; Publication (Box 686, Folder 6)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 686, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The African Development challenge, 1989; Publication (Box 686, Folder 7)
    Author: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 686, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Union Rights, 1988-2003 (Box 686, Folder 8)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Annual Survey of Violations of Trade Unions, 2004-2007 (Box 687, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Behind the Wire, 1996; Publication (Box 687, Folder 2)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: STOP Child Labour: The World's Best Kept Secret, 1994; Publication (Box 687, Folder 3)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: ICFTU/ETUC/USTMA Conference on Maghreb Migrant Workers in the EC, 1991; Publication (Box 687, Folder 4)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Educational News, 1960-1961 (Box 687, Folder 5)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Employment Manual, 1979; Publication (Box 687, Folder 6)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The European Trade Union Movement Within the ICFTU: Know Your Facts, 1964; Publication (Box 687, Folder 7)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Fighting for Workers' Human Rights in the Global Economy, 1998; Publication (Box 687, Folder 8)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Four Days of Freedom, 1957; Publication (Box 687, Folder 9)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1971; Publication (Box 687, Folder 10)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 687, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Free Labour World, 1950-1955 (Box 687, Folder 11)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 688, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Free Labour World, 1956-1961 (Box 688, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 689, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Free Labour World, 1962-1983 (Box 689, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Free Labour World, 1984; Publication (Box 690, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Railroad Wage Movement, 1941-1951 (Box 690, Folder 1)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: In the Fight for African Freedom, 1961; Publication (Box 690, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report of the General Secretary and Treasurer: Railroad Rules Wage Movement, 1946-1959 (Box 690, Folder 2)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: From the Ashes A Toy Factory in Thailand, 1994; Publication (Box 690, Folder 3)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Glossary of Trade Union Terms:Educational News, 1964; Publication (Box 690, Folder 4)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The French Trade Union Movement Past and Present, 1953; Publication (Box 690, Folder 5)
    Author: Georges Vidalenc
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Hind Mazdoor Sabha ICFTU, 1988; Publication (Box 690, Folder 6)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: ICFTU Briefing on Central and Eastern Europe, 1989-1990 (Box 690, Folder 7)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The First Ten Years, 1959; Publication (Box 690, Folder 8)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Views on the Economic and Social Situation in Asia, 1962; Publication (Box 690, Folder 9)
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: International and Comparative Social History, 2000; Publication (Box 690, Folder 10)
    Author: Anthony Carew: Michel Dreyfus: Geert Van Goethem: Rebecca Gumbrell-McCormick: Marcel van der Linden
- International Confederation of Free Trade Unions, Publication (Box 690, Folder 11)